Hey, hey
Hey
Don't want you, need you
Yeah, I need you to fill me up
Masigo masyeo bwado
Seonge chaji ana
Got a feeling that, oh, yeah (Yeah)
You could be everything that
That I need (Need), taste so sweet (Sweet)
Every sip makes me want more, yeah
Lookin like snacks 'cause you got it like that (Woo)
Take a big bite, want another bite, yeah
Neoui modeun geol nan wonhae, wonhae, wonhae
Neo malgon modu pyeonhae, pyeonhae, pyeonhae
Whеn you're in my arms
I hold you so tight (So tight)
Can't let go, no
No, not tonight
Jigeum dangjang nal bwa
Sigan еopjana
Neon naekkeoya imi
Algo itjana
'Cause I need you to need me
I'm empty, you feed me
So refreshing
My little soda pop
You're all I can think of
Every drop I drink up
You're my soda pop
My little soda pop
Cool me down, you're so hot
Pour me up, I won't stop
You're my soda pop
My little soda pop
Uh, make me wanna flip the top
Han mogeume you hit the spot
Every little drip and drop, fizz and pop, ah
Soreum doda it's gettin' hot
Yes, I'm sippin' when it's drippin' now
It's done? I need a second round
And pour a lot and don't you stop
'Til my soda pop fizzles out
Kkum soge geuryeowatdeon neo
Nan jeoldae nochil su eopseo
Neol wonhae kkok
I waited so long for a taste of soda
So, the wait is over, baby
Come and fill me up
Just can't get enough
Oh
You're all I can think of
Every drop I drink up
You're my soda pop
My little soda pop (Yeah, yeah)
Cool me down, you're so hot
Pour me up, I won't stop (Oh, oh)
You're my soda pop
My little soda pop
Ooh, ooh
You're my soda pop
Gotta drink every drop